Fata Sefer

Web-Developer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fata-sefer/ https://github.com/fs98

Travnik, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Location: Travnik, Bosnia an Phone: +387 62 808 723 E-mail: sefer.fata@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Web developer with Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology. Experienced working as a PHP Developer building web applications, mostly APIs, using Laravel framework. I am currently focused on improving my frontend skills.

Frontend: TypeScript, React, Next.js, Figma, Jest

Backend: PHP, Laravel, PHPUnit Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL

SKILLS

PHP • Laravel • PHPUnit • Rest API • TypeScript • Jest • JavaScript • React • Responsive Web Design • Tailwind CSS • SCSS • Database Management and Development

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Misija, Sarajevo, Bosnia

February 2022 – present

- Play a key role in designing and building APIs and Laravel Web Applications
- Participate in Frontend Development of React Apps
- Collaborate with Design team on a daily basis

Tech-stack: PHP, Laravel, REST API, PHPUnit, React, Vue, Figma, BitBucket

IT Specialist, Government of Central Bosnia Canton, Travnik, Bosnia

October 2021 - December 2021

Professional training program for college graduates.

- Worked in the IT sector.
- Was responsible for analysis, assessment and problem solving of a technical nature

Web Developer, Katriel Dev, Nova Bila, Bosnia

March 2019 - July 2021

- Started as an intern for three months
- Worked on the development of specific Internet applications under the mentorship of a more experienced colleague
- Uphold high standards for engineering and product quality. Apply this mindset through activities such as pair programming, code reviews etc.

Tech-stack: PHP, Laravel, Blade Templates, Bootstrap, Figma, GitHub

Active Projects

<u>http://www.katrieldev.com/</u> – Official Company Website – Laravel <u>http://www.franjinaekonomija.hr/</u> – Economy of Francesco – Laravel

EDUCATION

International University of Travnik - Faculty of Information Technology

October 2017 - July 2021

Bachelor of Information Technology, GPA: 9.54/10

Center for Lifelong Learning - educational program within the project "Young entrepreneurs, agents of change in the digital age"

October 2020 - May 2021

Educational program of three modules (leadership, graphic design, programming)

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Reading • Cake Decorating • Traveling • Cooking • Cats

LANGUAGES

Bosnian • English • German (B1) • French (A2)